<author lang="es">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lrainie: Hey #opendata nerds: Check out all the FREE @PewResearch data you can download at: https://t.co/CC01fMoy8U -  thanks to @PewMe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los 7 hábitos de las personas con inteligencia emocional #serfelizeneltrabajo via @silviasoria 
https://t.co/u2bRvDwy5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to this 2015 panel at @BeckerFriedman, Big Data analyzers, Statisticians and Economists will work together
https://t.co/fHLGbnmpyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sin #integridad, el profesor se convierte en un charlatán" @agalorda #educacion 
https://t.co/gluobw170x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @agalorda: ¿Qué esperas de un profesor? "Que me enseñe algo que no pueda encontrar en Google". http://t.co/GhVvMEIfLW | @unav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Vive con el inferior del modo como quieres que el superior viva contigo" - Séneca, 'Epístolas morales a Lucilio']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Si la sabiduría se me otorgase para mantenerla oculta, la rechazaría: sin compañía no es grata la posesión de bien alguno". - Séneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Doritos commercial to the revival of voluntarism, or how will trumps intellect
By @BishopBarron 
https://t.co/DnPsJGPVUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Differences among Americans &amp; European values - in a 2011 @pewresearch survey
https://t.co/SsbgJnGDAn https://t.co/JIDqVaxn1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamMGrant: Teaching kids to be grateful: give them less and let them cut their own vegetables. https://t.co/XxsVDX1I2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pewjournalism: Use of Twitter for news grew 2013-2015 among both users under 35 &amp; those 35+ https://t.co/gf37REyVPg https://t.co/P0WojK…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AspenInstitute: Better Work-Life Balance Doesn't Just Help Employees; it Helps the Whole Economy. https://t.co/lZebUDHV07 https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Deseamos algo porque lo juzgamos bueno, y no, al contrario, lo juzgamos bueno porque lo deseamos" - Aristóteles, en la 'Metafísica']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Los hombres comenzaron a filosofar al quedarse maravillados ante algo, (...) y después (...) ante cosas de mayor importancia". Aristóteles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Chesterton: "A man's conception of existence is the only important thing..." https://t.co/93Xjh6fFzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tanta belleza, contemplada desde aquella tierra desolada e inhóspita, le llegó al corazón [de Sam],y la esperanza renació en él #LeerTolkien]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Virpalpiv: "Sam, cuando las cosas están en peligro: alguien tiene que renunciar a ellas, perderlas para que otros las conserven"#LeerTo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pewresearch: There are major gaps between the public, scientists on key issues. Explore them here https://t.co/i95KmzWrUN https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accurate reflection on US Church by @PiadeSolenni, and I think the same ideas could be also said on the Spanish case
https://t.co/58RoVd3MOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No es lo mismo medir que evaluar. Para medir, indicadores; para evaluar, un directivo competente - via @MiguelArino
https://t.co/TQTViczEnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agreed https://t.co/B97wxNoIKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ManagersDiary: . https://t.co/H1gQm7YUqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Harvard: President Drew Faust spoke @WestPoint_USMA today about the value of the liberal arts. https://t.co/tBZikZQh1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s not business ethics. It’s just ethics - accountant who cooked the books and had enough of the lying
https://t.co/TQttgGnHUy  @GPHarvard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whorthwile reading it. At least, to have a different approach than the prevalent one https://t.co/SgAXMg7gWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review on a book I recently read: "How The West Really Lost God" by Mary Eberstadt. Answer: family. 
https://t.co/tr02q4C3x4 via @PhilCooke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worthwile reading: how Mulally changed Ford culture by aligning employee efforts toward a meaningful def of success
https://t.co/Ut4EAY59kp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porque sabes, puedes y debes escribir - Palabras a Tolkien de su futura mujer al regalarle una pluma x su 18 cumple 
https://t.co/0JwTxRrLxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rsalaverria: Hoy se distinguen muy bien tres tipos medios: los que te alertan, los que te lo confirman y -los más escasos- los que te a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OUPPhilosophy: Read about Elizabeth Anscombe's life and work https://t.co/06bQf3nYLb via Oxford Reference #womeninphilosophy #WomensHis…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most informed advice I can give leaders is “Love your people" - Thanks, @MarkCCrowley ! - https://t.co/WqBpKX5lU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our home is that thing to which we can dedicate our energies with such devotion that the ultimate results become inconsequential @GilbertLiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GilbertLiz at TED: Build your house right on top of the worthiest thing that you love most
https://t.co/d1aYYPTXrp via @AdamMGrant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good advice from @CHunterArscott: Ask women in your company, don't presuppose their expectations
https://t.co/pUgQPUdf73 via @AdamMGrant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord Of The Rings: How Music Elevates Story via @SocTolkien 
https://t.co/Ohojc2aoKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maredata: una iniciativa de Fernanda Peset @UPV para ofrecer en abierto los datos de las investigaciones. Gracias!
https://t.co/n8DwyLSsO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Esta tarde imparto el seminario @IecoInstitute sobre el artículo de E. Anscombe "Moral Modern Philosophy" en @UV_EG https://t.co/3tG3nDrvO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 keys to #Forgiveness, by Robert Enright @UWMadEducation. Highly recommended - @GreaterGoodSC 
https://t.co/1ZzCVK4rKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When life hits us hard, there is nothing as effective as forgiveness for healing deep wounds" - Robert Enright https://t.co/1ZzCVK4rKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on forgiveness can reverse the lies we often tell ourselves when someone has hurt us deeply, like "I’m not worthy" - Robert Enright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Morafandos Lo sé: disfruté mucho leyendo el libro de @monicacodina "El sigilo de la memoria". Muy recomendable para saber + de Dostoievski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anteayer conocí a Mónica Codina, profesora de @fcomunav, experta en ética de la comunicación https://t.co/u71hYGkImk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Deberían haberme advertido que convertirme en madre lo cambiaría todo"
https://t.co/xp3iQoRnMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Una alumna del Master Com Cientifica @UniversidadVIU ha lanzado este blog de Ciencia. Enhorabuena, Rocío! @yupiay https://t.co/de3M9k1FDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quien te enfada, te controla. Pero sobre todo, nuestro buen (o mal) humor no puede depender de otro - @MiguelArino https://t.co/2As7Y4P3Uj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BreneBrown: Vulnerability paradox: Vulnerability is the the first thing I look for in you and the last thing I want you to see in me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scruton_Quotes: "By seeing something as beautiful, you lift it out of the practical arena and endow it with a worth that cannot be surr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Si decidimos inclinarnos hacia el don, nuestro día estará marcado por mayores éxitos y logrará un impacto + duradero https://t.co/Vj1M9sk49R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some studies show that teens who find pleasure in giving to others may be protected from developing depression https://t.co/0PdCFDYVr5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harvard professor Mary Gaylord reads Don Quixote every year, and she speaks on Cervantes as if they were friends!
https://t.co/OyMZ5Q1A2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way we work depends mainly on how we understand ourserlves and how we organize institutions @BarrySch https://t.co/UinVrRMmXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamMGrant: How to win the career lottery, with @chrisguillebeau &amp; @susancain: https://t.co/KyYVdmCCtH https://t.co/gnst7vPlNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Morafandos: Lo que encuentro insoportable es el pesimismo complacido de algunos intelectuales que se regocijan con el mal. Claudio Magr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me temo que leer resulta "peligroso" cada vez más... #DiaDelLibro
https://t.co/tOQHUgj8et https://t.co/1wmF6wWf8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GuillermoLPD: Del 16 al 18 de noviembre, el @grupomediaflows organiza en la UIMP de Valencia un Congreso de comunicación política y TICs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamMGrant: If you want people to be generous, you don't need to offer incentives. You just need to remove the disincentives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El negativo efecto de un absorbente horario laboral x parte de los directivos, de JM Fdez-Crehuet
https://t.co/339YyvK6va via @moviecoaching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonHaidt: How university students came to believe that there was a bureaucratic solution for every problem: https://t.co/dmtN4zBJfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamMGrant: "A life is not important except in the impact it has on other lives."
#JackieRobinsonDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suggestive orientations for taking good decisions when we prepare data for analysis and when we use analytics tools
https://t.co/ur7vIlBTBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders often share a common trait: a gift for language, and a capacity to compel others through the spoken word
https://t.co/P3aGfIV9XS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamMGrant, a social scientist who wants to bring data to the leaders in order to take better decisions
https://t.co/CoIhKwWgI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parece que alguien es capaz de explicar la relación entre ética y buen trabajo @DrHowardGardner via @AmparoFerrandoR https://t.co/jGziROqg6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A subtle revolution: We've drifted from having a market economy to becoming market societies - M Sandel at @TEDTalks https://t.co/s1RfxOOA1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Esta semana se han cumplido 73 años de "El Principito": 9 lecciones de este gran libro via @cg_heredia y Twitter
https://t.co/CtOKxDSmnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Forgiveness: Why is something so good for us so hard to do? @LindaGrahamMFT points out 3 barriers in https://t.co/daoMG3wyr2 @GreaterGoodSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["El instrumento más eficaz para la vida feliz se halla en la convicción de que el único bien es la honestidad" Séneca - Epístolas a Lucilio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Power: the more I give, the less I have; Love: the more I share, the more I have" - @RabbiSacks via @templeton_fdn
https://t.co/jg6KCtAOfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning to judge music? Yes, because "Judgment is the precondition of true enjoyment" @Roger_Scruton #education https://t.co/HAGZ3UY5dc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BigDataSoc: How do Politicians use Facebook? An Applied Social Observatory https://t.co/RVOimbmEGZ @SAGESociology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To boost our creativity, @AdamMGrant suggests embrace the fear of failing to try. See https://t.co/iOwU2mXiEk #TED https://t.co/MOqC7m9vZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turning to Aquinas on Virtue: a suggestive lecture by @CandaceVogler at @ThomisticInst #podcast
https://t.co/fP4rjaf3xS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Sandel: There is a tremendous hunger to engage in reasoned public debate about moral and spiritual questions
https://t.co/a8Q06m8Qk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nature contributes to a healthier, happier &amp; + creative life. Yes! That's an overwhelming experience for every hiker
https://t.co/dW0HZgsJm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Escribir, leer, volver a leer y volver a escribir: son los recursos del pensar" @JaimeNubiola #VidaIntelectual
https://t.co/8evG22zLbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Useful tool: 'Practical Data Science in Python'. I have learned a lot
Thanks, @RadimRehurek
https://t.co/5qH2RXhtc7 https://t.co/4wPEIVEsRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pewresearch: 10 demographic trends that are shaping the U.S. and the world https://t.co/MXGrNc9b3s https://t.co/9qjSAZ9O7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The man who has not suffered - what can he possible know, anyway?’ Rabbi Abraham Heschel via @PKreeft1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Friday, at @EconomUnav, I will present my paper on the Logic of Gift, published on Business Ethics Quarterly https://t.co/6CPGy7vREZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychological safety is a belief that one will not be humiliated for speaking up with concerns - Prof. Amy Edmonson
https://t.co/OcPzJSDwXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you want to build a company to last +100 years? Read Aristotle. That is what Brunello Cucinelli did
@ryanjstelzer https://t.co/TLo6h3JcwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does bring us deep happiness? Aquinas points to the striving for the Truth and for the Good - Fr. Joseph White
https://t.co/O43SKplOH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google asked: What does a team make to thrive? After a huge amount of data, the answer was: psychological safety!
https://t.co/OZDXMOyZIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mmm! Project Aristotle at Google. It seems wisdom can help us to work with people. Just Emotional Intelligence. Easy https://t.co/do0jYD9MSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prof. Anthony Esolen at @ThomisticInst: Education should teach "how to love Beauty, Goodness, Truth" #Dante #Aquinas
https://t.co/rs2JDHsO4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps business success may be achieved by focusing more on building a 'beautiful company' 
https://t.co/f59yfvmJEO https://t.co/5mKEllM6aW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting book: "Finding True Happiness: Satisfying Our Restless Hearts"
Interview with the author Robert Spitzer:
https://t.co/JLbwA2aZ2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El auge de las academias en la universidad: ¿escaso nivel d secundaria o calidad docente poco transparente? @elmundo
https://t.co/51a3ViFGnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They Lived in Hovels but Built Cathedrals: a compelling interview to prof. Saltamacchia - #podcast @Creighton
https://t.co/qz3DezsWoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Un testimonio de lo que supone dejarse arrastrar por una adicción a las apuestas deportivas - via @elmundoes https://t.co/7eDY4y3mjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[¿Es posible actualmente una actitud intelectual que no "ahogue" el misterio? @pablo_dors reflexiona certeramente en https://t.co/tABPvLBN2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @grupomediaflows: https://t.co/90DAaSUwzM https://t.co/bJP0rClj7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mujer de rojo sobre fondo gris" - una de esas novelas que, después de leerla, te la llevas adentro - via @vibusg  https://t.co/VRcTW5Mpgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who was Aquinas? How should we begin to read Summa Theologiae? @BishopBarron offers illuminating answers @WordOnFire https://t.co/rXcB7knUaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amywrzesniewski speaks on how we can work with a greater purpose #podcast #meaningfulwork
https://t.co/oE72rWYknH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amywrzesniewski speaks on the way people work when they view their job as a calling @HiddenBrain #meaningfulwork
https://t.co/piCJL0Ekcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El próximo viernes 6-may impartiré un seminario sobre Aristóteles en el @CMUAlbalat (Valencia) 19:00 #AñoAristoteles https://t.co/nrtyNcTlIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reflection on the importance of facts and not ideology for children education by @ACPeds
https://t.co/lSlWlgFYpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty Matters: it amplifies our joys as it reveals a truly lovable reality. 
From @Roger_Scruton's documentary https://t.co/a4dSMYULzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La maternidad embellece  
https://t.co/xe8qpbbP06 #DiaDeLaMadre https://t.co/P9L5mOFcCC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>