<author lang="es">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Según @NuriaChinchilla, la gente no se va de las empresas, se va de los jefes https://t.co/nMVkn3RuP5 via @vibusg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alfvara: Tremenda gráfica. 
Más muertos que recién nacidos. 
vía @Porcentuales https://t.co/HTfKVS1FZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prof Harvey Mansfield: the lack of devotion to learning is a result of having stopped pursuing truth by its own sake
https://t.co/X2B7AvGSXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some data science skills and several interesting resources @analyticbridge via @ScienceFlows
https://t.co/aqNHx8mGXV https://t.co/6UKIXF0dIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CatedraTEF_UA: Habilidades más populares en #DataScience https://t.co/ojpLDhxR9K @analyticbridge https://t.co/eEDh2JoC9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La diferencia entre las Humanidades y las carreras de Letras, bien explicada por José María Torralba, prof. de @unav
https://t.co/r4jqU5OQ79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biografía íntima de la primera onda gravitacional: buen artículo de @nunodomin sobre el experimento #LIGO @el_pais
https://t.co/t7Hcac5kFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not good news for any democracy. https://t.co/DcJAUn4wz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @franmartin24: https://t.co/H5dkf0skZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rsalaverria: 24% de los españoles lee noticias en inglés. Más que en cualquiera de las lenguas propias, salvo el español #DNP2016 https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Business of Life: Another way of learning from economic theories to lead oneself - @HarvardHBS @claychristensen 
https://t.co/nuKaIK9LRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @grupomediaflows: Cómo y de qué hablaron Iglesias, Sánchez, Rivera y Rajoy en Twitter en la campaña del 20D https://t.co/dvcH8YK0Eb por…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ‘Logic of Gift’: Inspiring Behavior in Organizations Beyond the Limits of Duty and Exchange. Published in BEQ https://t.co/nZcstZAYr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesante reflexión de @JaimeNubiola sobre la amabilidad en la docencia
https://t.co/kjoJNuSB9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Media exposure is arguably the most important" indicator of success in the 'invisible primary' @tompharvard's study https://t.co/mYKZOqMg4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ocho gráficos que explican la transformación del periodismo. Por @jagaraviles - @mipumh 
https://t.co/fERox0199l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Print media's relevance is waning in front of online media. Turning point in #journalism. By @jagaraviles - @mipumh https://t.co/ZHaZNlCQ9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom of Conscience or gender preferences? It seems it is at stake the same human rights system @tsurenweber &amp; Lin https://t.co/tLWP3k7vbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Spain, 47% agree with "You can trust most news most of the time". Not bad, but this points to a true challenge https://t.co/y45vxKCrWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where did transgenderism come from? According to Mark Regnerus, "framing" has played a major role, instead of debate
https://t.co/OGeYFnZlNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UChiVirtue: Sherwin quotes Brubeck to illustrate virtues transformation-&gt; Jazz has something all people need to succeed: Freedom within…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The second workshop of the @UChiVirtue project is working right now in this kind of topics. #VHML16 #BestInvestment https://t.co/IX7M7Sgvmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we have the basic ideas of human action in Aquinas. Fantastic! https://t.co/9ALwHPuTLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UChiVirtue: Acquiring virtues is a question of making good choices, which will eventually have a resulting good effect on your characte…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @moviecoaching: #LesMiserables https://t.co/84FjfWBTJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is a healthy culture? Prof Anthony Esolen helps us by pointing to ordinary things &amp; making compelling questions
https://t.co/XdRH8d4duO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too much of a good thing: a psychology paper on Aristotle by @AdamMGrant  and @BarrySch https://t.co/SkPClRxnvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking on authenticity: an interesting debate between @AdamMGrant and @BreneBrown. Thanks to both of you!
https://t.co/rakU9LsdMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BenjaminBathke: Key findings of 2016 Reuters Institute Digiral News Report #GENsummit #DigitalNewsReport https://t.co/rLMQo00sPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maturity and Enthusiasm: key values of those who return to work after a career break #TED Carol F. Cohen #childcare
https://t.co/WOCDg7ug8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mmm... Algunos directivos "sucumben" por la adicción del dinero, y tb por la presión del sistema. Via @moviecoaching https://t.co/0fm3LPE5p2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @yonitter: "Single-tasking means doing one activity at a time with as few distractions and interruptions as possible." https://t.co/Abxm…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesante herramienta para esta campaña. via @yonitter https://t.co/HF8jPeasKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good example of recovering wisdom https://t.co/ts4qIItHZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Altruistic Personality: What led ordinary Men &amp; Women to risk their life on behalf of others?" #Goodreads https://t.co/Io2IukA9bz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rescuers of Jews remind us that moral courage is available to all through the quality of ordinary human interactions- Altruistic Personality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably one of the most needed skills today is... having a conversation. Remarkable #TED Talk by @CelesteHeadlee https://t.co/EyJOXG6nh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ideas are more precious than diamonds". These are the most precious ideas for Peter Kreeft, @BostonCollege
https://t.co/KQH1gGKZRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 tips to spread better a good idea, or how to transform your idea into a gift to the audience - Head #TED @TEDchris https://t.co/UdXuCGEYkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Las posibilidades que España tiene de llegar a ser una potencia científica: 0
@enriquegimberna via Luis Chiva
https://t.co/OQPinB3dM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UChiVirtue: Vogler: Anscombe gained traction because everyone was hungry for questions to help us think about how to lead a good human…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we outsource our responsibility, who will want to bring up children? Remarkable reflection by @rabbisacks #Crisis https://t.co/ydtFbXgcVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insightful article on True Friendship and Marriage based on Aristotle's teaching. By Angela Knobel @PublicDiscourse https://t.co/xlxQ2MXjyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totalmente de acuerdo, @MonicadelaOliva. via @vibusg https://t.co/B9qOR1vhtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julia Rozovsky and her team at @google identified the 5 key traits for a successful team
https://t.co/4Dd0fMHqfH https://t.co/mmsUrhlVcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamMGrant: You have a to-do list, but do you have a never-to-do list?
Write down the choices that would compromise your values. https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aristóteles nos enseñó a pensar, y a distinguir entre mera instrucción y sabiduría perenne. Via @miriamrevert 
https://t.co/CWcqhLwecU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can gender engineering be unmasked? Through recovering the sexual dimension in human beings - @Stella_Morabito https://t.co/VwJ27F252V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who want to have an impact tend to identify with a kind of narrative: redemptive. Dan McAdams at @UChiVirtue https://t.co/A9WwWWANJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mbaipade: #LifeStyle: Now that your are familiar with #burnout, learn how to avoid it: https://t.co/4JhCL1tfpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engagement or Burnout? Good infographic from @mbaipade to discern the causes https://t.co/41U53HP5nY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vaya! Hay gente "real" que opta por subir el salario de su equipo antes que su propio beneficio - via @javipial92 https://t.co/yQYDtq4IyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worthwhile lecture by @Yale Prof Steven Smith: In Defense of #Politics. #patriotism #justice #CivicEducation
https://t.co/fSUqIXm9rh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Neumann: nothing could be more important to kids than that they learn how to be philosophers - @washingtonpost
https://t.co/QLIwN9xiqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very useful suggestions to the #maths needed in #MachineLearning. It includes a list of several #MOOCs - @Rbloggers
https://t.co/tj8L59ifg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ecogranjero: "¿Qué es el infierno? Yo sostengo que es el sufrimiento de ser incapaz de amar" - Fiodor Dostoievski https://t.co/c21u7v79…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am working right now with #Gephi, and I have found this PDF very useful. Thanks to @seinecle
https://t.co/7CRMjdWquk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Awakening of Miss Prim”: A Breath of Fresh Sanity, by Joseph Pearce @imaginativecons 
https://t.co/fNKQ7RGsZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remarkable quotes from "The Awakening of Miss Prim": #beaty, #admiration, #marriage, #sacrifice... #GoodReads
https://t.co/yYNN96ia85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suggestive paper on Aristotle, Aquinas and Anscombe by @CandaceVogler, with an interesting reflection on Thomas More
https://t.co/5XQn0kiAZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytdavidbrooks "If you expect people to be selfish, you can actually crush their tendency to be good" #Altruism
https://t.co/5qDvdPyBlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American younger generations tend to search for online news @pewjournalism https://t.co/v9ao0OY4GF https://t.co/5H1XGAt1pO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another way of searching for trustworthy information sources: how much disinterested is the author? @DrHowardGardner
https://t.co/akXTWweTwm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 #buenaslecturas para el verano: En lugar seguro, Dar y recibir, El precio a pagar, y 2+...
https://t.co/FsX5Vp4ZIx https://t.co/yEhwxfVp6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[¿Para qué sirve la #literatura a un ingeniero? - seminario que impartí en @tecnun hace 2 años #humanidades
https://t.co/wUDKY6h9IG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Claves para disfrutar de las novelas de #JaneAusten: humor, ironía, autocaracterización, complicidad..
https://t.co/94SLyfLTzI @M_A_JORDAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How @nytdavidbrooks prepares his columns - @aspenideas Jobs as a Vocation: Finding Meaning in Our Work - @ChipCutter
https://t.co/1LhKnzBqr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acabo de subir a @academia el ensayo "La grandeza de la libertad en #ElSenorDeLosAnillos" Fue #PremiosAelfwine 2009
https://t.co/6xrBEQ7oeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can a transactional environment be a place for friendship? It may be if we cultivate proper connections @AdamMGrant 
https://t.co/eqrWzG5MWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just uploaded 'The 'Logic of Gift': Inspiring Behavior in Organizations Beyond the Limits of Duty…' to @academia https://t.co/mDzSRF9c3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Steiner: Yo soy tan solo un cartero. Y estoy muy orgulloso de haber llevado el correo bien a tantos alumnos. 
https://t.co/Ot8MgIF0dE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversación política en Facebook: Buen reportaje sobre estrategia electoral del 26J por @Mart1nMucha @javiernegre10
https://t.co/9o9o08lRbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muere Elie Wiesel, superviviente de Auschwitz y premio Nobel de la Paz: "si olvidamos, somos cómplices” via @el_pais
https://t.co/zq0mcPxyBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we predict in advance what direction our life is likely to be? @claychristensen on how to lead a happier life
https://t.co/JhOXz6ol14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting healthy limits: Five Research-Based Ways to Say No, by @raisinghappines @GreaterGoodSC #happiness https://t.co/R4vz0PWoaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Sherwin lectures on love in Aquinas, &amp; his elaboration through Augustine &amp; Aristotle #podcast @ThomisticInst https://t.co/RbWXON5nQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnvoyColorado Good point of helping your team members. Congrats for your post!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conditions for #teamwork: compelling direction, strong structure, supportive context and shared mindset @HarvardBiz
https://t.co/tSZhh7lCWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hybrid Media System: #PoliticalCommunication where online and mainstream media are intertwined @andrew_chadwick
https://t.co/7gkDOvYawU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 tips to Cultivate Ethical Courage: learn your patterns, listen to your body &amp; commitment @brookend @GreaterGoodSC
https://t.co/1AkSwe8kUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rsalaverria: España se confirma como potencia en estudios sobre Comunicación: 3ª mundial, solo detrás de USA y UK, según SCImago. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jasepuch: The most successful videos 
-short
-designed to work w/ no sound 
-focus on soft news
-w/ a strong emotional element https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasing trend of getting news from Facebook by younger generations. #journalism #newsconsumption @pewjournalism https://t.co/Cave9R7POp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These styles of reciprocity are very well delineated in @AdamMGrant's book "Give and Take" https://t.co/6TqkzaGWZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pregunta del profesor @JaimeNubiola, de @unav: ¿Por qué buscamos la #belleza? Respuesta: porque nos cura. Pero hay +
https://t.co/GxqQ2hfYpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DataAnalytics in #politics: good article by @kreissdaniel on the different strategies between US candidates
https://t.co/p0orfEQ128]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A recent finding: The School for Ethical Education: "Ethics in action creates character". Many interesting resources
https://t.co/sqytQGoCqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pabeard2911: "Character is knowing the good,
loving the good and doing the good."
Thomas Lickona]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @biblioenlace: Tal día como hoy nació uno de los más grandes, Jorge Luis #Borges. https://t.co/9KT1VQ71Ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libro disfrutado en agosto: "Mi lucha contra Hitler", de Dietrich von Hildebrand https://t.co/Y4jBmbYkUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GPHarvard: Study finds only 30% of workers are purpose-oriented, but that 30% is more engaged and performs better: https://t.co/D9PjDiX…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Divine" comment on Dante's "Divine Comedy" @WordOnFire by @BishopBarron #GreatBooks
https://t.co/Yy33msUTqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mbaipade: How constitutes an emotional salary? https://t.co/nsC8nrfd9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Génesis del concepto de Interés Propio, por Germán Scalzo
Texto recomendable para relacionar sobre Adam Smith &amp; co.
https://t.co/nRdqLWvxa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dan McAdams on The Generative Adult, or the commitment to promoting the well-being of future generations @UChiVirtue https://t.co/Jqd25hwUxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From "An Everyone Culture" by Kegan &amp; Lahey: Becoming a Deliberately Developmental Organization. #Happiness at #Work https://t.co/4K6dQoDa5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would it look like to “do work” in a way that every partner is involved in each other’s flourishing? It's real https://t.co/coPZmGZNQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["La manzana de Newton, o cómo se descubrió la Ley de Gravitación Universal" por Shahen Hacyan #divulgacioncientifica
https://t.co/VniR92MjRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RecommendedBook "Immunity to Change" by Robert Kegan &amp; Lisa L. Lahey #mentaldevelopment Thanks to @drdonnahicks https://t.co/uUEKS1IB5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do individuals who desire to do good work succeed or fail at a time when market forces are powerful? @GPHarvard
https://t.co/JbJzqfT8Yk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>